What are you doing?
Nothing. I thought
I heard Brandon crying.
You going someplace?
No.
No. I'm not.
What's in the bag?
Nothing its just
Brandon's belongings.
It's Brandon's.
What's in the bag.
Please.
It's nothing.
Sam. please.
I--
Please. for me.
Please.
Mrs. Labon.
I was asking
if she has a name yet.
Yes.
Natasha.
She's beautiful.
Thank you.
Do the doctors know
why she was born premature?
Not yet.
Have you been under any
kind of stress
lately?
Why?
Well. stress and anxiety
can be one
of the causes
of premature birth.
She's a tough girl.
only seven months
in and she's ready to take
on the world.
Or maybe it was
just too painful to stay inside.
You know.
Albert Einstein. Isaac Newton
and Stevie Wonder
were all premature babies.
I'd say that's not
a coincidence.
They were all fighting
for their lives
since the day they were born.
You seem like a fighter too.
Did you hear that?
You're a fighter like Mama?
It was 1987. Iranian New Year.
We were celebrating Nowruz
with dates back over 3000 years.
Its purpose is to celebrate
the beginning of Spring.
the renewal of nature.
It symbolized much more
than that.
It was a passing of the torch.
When the older family members
would shower
the young generation
with money and gifts.
All Iranians loved to entertain.
Whenever the doorbell rang.
I ran to see who had arrived.
and in typical Iranian fashion.
welcomed everyone with kisses.
Those years were surrounded
by family at love.
During the reign
of the late Shah of Iran.
many sought change
and believed Islamists
would bring a better life
to the people of Iran.
The revolution
abolished the monarchy
and the Ayatollah.
the religious Muslim
fundamentalists
seized power.
However. the outcome was far
from what people had hoped for.
Violence
and disarray ensued.
and people's freedom
was gradually shipped away.
especially those of women.
My beloved daughter Darya
always wanted
to become a doctor.
She was eight years old
when the bombings of the cities
and civilians intensified.
It was that day.
I decided it was time
for my daughter
to leave Iran for good.
Hello.
Take off those headphones.
please.
Headphones off.
Good girl.
It's for your own benefit.
You'll thank me later.
My God. what are you watching?
World War II?
No.
It's Tehran
during the Iran-Iraq War.
Mom. were you there?
Where?
Oh. yes.
Yes. I was.
I lost my best friend there.
actually.
Our school was blown up. too.
She was only 12.
Damn.
How did you get out?
I was one of the lucky ones.
I guess.
It's okay. I'm here.
That's hard to watch.
I got it.
Hi.
Is your mom home?
Mom?
Yes.
The police are here.
What's going on?
Hi. can I help you?
Darya Labon?
Yes. it's Davoudi now.
my maiden name.
Ms. Davoudi. my name is
Detective Emmanuel Goddard.
LAPD homicide.
This is my partner.
Detective Janet Carter.
May we speak to you in private.
please?
Sure.
Can you go up to your rooms.
please?
-Mom.
-It's okay.
Go ahead.
It's okay.
Please. come in.
Thank you.
Would you like to have a seat?
No. thank you.
Ms. Davoudi.
Gosh. no easy way to say this.
I'm going
to come right out with it.
We believe your life
is in danger
and that someone wants
to harm you.
Harm me?
Who?
Why?
What's your relationship like
with your ex-husband. Sam Labon?
Why are you asking me
about Sam?
Is he okay. or--
When's the last time
you spoke to him?
He actually
just recently helped my father
with something
with his passport.
What is this about?
Ms. Davoudi. your ex-husband
has put a hit out on your life.
I'm sorry. what?
He made a credible attempt
to hire a hitman to torture
and kill you.
Sam?
No. that's not possible.
I know my ex-husband.
He can be intense at times.
but he would never do anything
like that.
-Is there any reason
why you think he'd want
to do this to you?
No.
I don't know.
Everything is fine.
Our divorce was just finalized
two weeks ago.
and the judge
actually ordered him
to pay me $2.5 million.
but I ended up forgiving that.
I let him keep the property.
and there must be some mistake.
We have something to show you.
I want to warn you.
it won't be easy to watch.
- I want the face.
the legs. the back.
the spine all messed up.
and permanent damage.
I need to know
when it's going to happen.
because I need an alibi. right?
I need her hurt
from her spine to her knees.
You want me to kill her?
If she dies.
I got no problem with that.
Okay.
Can I get you anything.
water. tea. anything?
Ms. Davoudi.
we can help you.
We're going to need to find
some place where you
and your children can stay.
Oh. no. I'm not leaving.
This is my home.
Where am I supposed to go?
My kids are in school.
Why can't you
just arrest him now.
you have this video?
No arrest
can be made at this time.
but I guarantee you.
we are monitoring him.
What is important is that you
and your children find
some place that you can stay
for a few weeks.
This can't be happening.
I'm not doing that.
Why don't you and your kids
pack up some things
and we will escort you
to the airport.
You want us to leave right now?
Ms. Davoudi. a credible threat
has been made upon your life.
and I can guarantee
these guys do not wait around.
I suggest you pack light.
you leave your phones
and other electronic devices.
and you meet us outside.
Detective.
She had no idea.
Didn't she?
Mom. is everything okay?
We have to leave.
We have to leave now.
I need you to pack a bag.
both of you.
Okay. bring only what you need.
-What did the police say?
-Why? What's going on?
Just bring
some clothes for a week or two.
Bring your school stuff.
Don't forget your school stuff.
Do not bring
your phones. actually.
Leave your phones here.
Look. you hear me?
- You're scaring us.
Look. please. just do as I say.
I will explain later.
And hurry.
Okay.
Here. give me those.
Thank you. You guys get in.
I got it.
-Thank you.
Mom.
you got to tell
us what's going on now.
They think someone
wants to harm me.
What?
Who?
That's all I'm going to say.
Mom. who?
-Hey. is it Dad?
-I can't breathe.
I can't breathe.
-Mom.
-Hey. you're okay.
-It's okay.
-You're okay.
-Please breathe with us.
- You got to get in.
Okay. yes.
Mom. we got to go. Okay?
we got to go.
Yes. go ahead.
Come in.
It's sorted.
This is a burner phone.
This is how we reach you
when you land.
Keep it someplace safe.
Where are we going?
To a friend's.
You said you had
a friend in Miami?
Yes. I do.
Call them
and we'll book you
on the next flight out.
And kids. don't call
your dad.
- Darya. welcome to Miami.
Oh. my God. I'm so glad
you had me so worried.
Oh. you have no idea
how much this means to me
and to all of us. really.
It's always good
to see you. Dee.
You. too.
And you two.
My God. you're getting
taller by the day.
-Yes?
-Yes.
Just wait till I get you
on the court.
Challenge accepted.
Look at this lovely lady.
Hi.
Okay. talk to me.
What's going on?
Later. Can we actually--
Can we go up to the rooms?
Yes. sure.
We're already checked in.
so I got everything.
Let's go.
Follow me.
Come on. guys.
All right. there we go.
I don't understand.
I don't believe it.
The fact that he would want
to harm me
or kill me.
Really?
The mother of his children.
It doesn't feel real.
Yeah. I know. I know.
I'm glad you came to me.
Look at this.
I forgot so many things.
I don't even know what I packed.
All right. look.
why don't I go out
and I'll pick up anything you
and the kids need. okay?
You're the best.
Damn straight.
I'll be back.
Okay.
You good. Mom?
Yes.
I'm fine.
How about you?
I'm okay.
Yes?
Yes.
I think I'm just going
to take my ball out.
try to see
if I can find somewhere to shoot
some hoops.
-No my love.
I need you to stay here. please.
Why?
No one knows us here.
Brandon. please.
Just for now.
We need
to stay inside together. okay?
Do you wish
you never moved here?
To the States I mean.
No.
No. of course not.
Your father
gave me two
of my greatest gifts.
you and Natasha.
I will never regret that.
Now. is
the relationship complicated?
Yes.
But listen.
I know deep in my heart
that your father
loves you both very much. okay?
I believe that. and you need
to believe that. too.
What was he
like when you met him?
That is the most beautiful girl
I've ever seen
in my entire life.
I think I'm in love.
You know what?
I'm going to get a drink
and ask her to dance.
Yes. that's what I'm going
to do.
Sweetheart.
Where are you from?
Take a guess?
How did you know?
You speak Persian?
A little bit.
I can learn a little more.
It's not that easy.
Maybe you could teach me.
I'm not that easy. either.
One dance. one dance.
Come on. one dance.
Please.
Come on.
Hey. I'm going to go
to the bathroom.
I'll be back. okay?
-You sneaked me on that. bro.
-Oh. man. I'm so sorry.
Listen. I had to.
Okay. but at least tell me
you got her number.
I'm about to.
Don't worry. I'm about to.
-All right. don't fail me them.
Sorry I had to sneak in there.
Hey.
She's with me.
Am I?
Am I what?
With you?
I don't know.
Do you want to be?
Huh?
I don't know.
Maybe you could give me
your number
and we could find out.
Wow. getting
right to the point.
I see.
I don't have a pen.
Hey. sorry.
Let me borrow this.
Please.
I'm resourceful.
I almost gave up
my life for you.
You see that?
He's very mad at me.
I keep the pen.
See you later.
Hey. wait.
The last digit is missing.
I told you I'm not that easy.
Today is one
of the happiest days
for our family.
Our beloved daughter. Darya.
is getting married.
the apple of our eyes.
You two
met each other and fell in love.
This is truly love
at first sight.
We wish you a long.
happy. progressive life.
Hopefully with lots of children.
inshallah.
Two things
you should never forget.
First and foremost.
do not stop coming around
and sharing your life.
Do not stop talking.
Not talking is dangerous.
Now.
allow me to officiate
your wedding.
Sam.
the ladies who are stubbing
sugar over your head
are symbolically wishing
you a sweet life full of love.
Now. the moment
we have all been waiting for
has arrived.
Darya.
do you take Sam
as your lawfully wedded husband
until death do you part?
The bride is going to bring
some flowers. she says.
Okay. I'll ask again.
Darya. do you take Sam
as your lawfully wedded husband
until death do you part?
Darya.
look at him.
He's begging.
Bravo.
Darya. this is your last chance.
Third time.
Do you take Sam
as your lawfully wedded husband
until death do you part?
Yes. I do.
Wait. wait.
We have to wait for Sam.
Sam.
do you take Darya
as your lawfully wedded wife
until death do you part?
Of course I do.
Yes.
I now pronounce you
man and wife.
Congratulations.
Hey. Darya.
I got you some things
and soups on.
Stop starving me.
All right. you jackass.
Thanks. Max.
You're welcome.
It smells good.
-Can we eat?
-Yes. go ahead.
Hey.
I was thinking.
What's going on?
Nothing. but I was
thinking maybe
we should move
around a little bit.
just for safety's sake.
What do you mean?
Where will we move to?
I've got
a client who's got a house
on the beach in Fort Lauderdale.
I don't think
they can track you there.
Max. I can't ask you
to do that.
No. don't worry.
They're not even there.
In fact. they hate tour season.
Every November to March.
it's empty.
and that's why I think
it's the perfect place
to hide out.
I think it's for the best.
Okay.
We'll go early in the morning.
-Okay.
-All right.
Don't eat it all.
Oh. look at that.
I always thought
I was one of the lucky ones.
What do you mean?
I'm lucky to be able
to leave Iran.
Not everyone can do that.
but then what?
I mean all these years
of violence and abuse
and now divorced
without a child support.
Look. I try my best.
but it's not fair. you know?
It's not fair to the kids.
- Jesus.
What the hell?
What is it?
It's kids.
It's fireworks.
It's okay.
-I'm so paranoid.
-Yes. I know.
He got me.
You got one now. too.
Wow.
Here we go.
Home sweet home.
You said that
at the last house. so.
Yes.
Okay.
Kids.
rooms are in the back.
Go choose yours.
-I get first pick.
-No. ladies first. dude.
- Hi. Darya.
It's Detective Goddard.
How are you doing?
Honestly.
I really can't take this.
If he doesn't kill me.
the stress will.
I hear you.
Unfortunately.
the police department
doesn't provide
personal security
for incidents like yours.
I wish we did.
but we don't.
You've had a lot of cases
like this before?
No. Every case is different.
Some men can never accept
that they have a problem.
they think physical abuse
is normal.
Right?
They don't want to take
measures needed to solve
the issues or to heal.
Can't accept that they've lost
their wife or kids.
It all comes down to envy
or hate or control
or lack of it.
It's a cycle of trauma.
If they can't have you.
no one else will.
Have I cheered you up yet?
- Oh. yes. You're doing
a great job.
Thanks.
Basically.
I'll just be another statistic.
Yes. well. it's my job
to make sure
that doesn't happen.
Where are you now?
We're in Fort Lauderdale.
I can get you the address.
No. not over the phone.
The place you're staying.
you're with your friend?
Yes.
A friend of Max.
This Max can be trusted?
Yes. of course.
Had to ask.
Look. we're working on stuff
on our end. okay?
Just hang in there.
Okay.
That's reassuring.
Yes. right.
Just keep me posted. please?
Oh. you'll be
the first to know.
Thank you. Detective.
Call me Manny.
Thanks. Manny.
See you now.
That Davoudi woman. I assume?
It's easy for you to say.
How's she holding up?
Oh. the best she can.
Not every day
the father of your children
wants you tortured and murdered.
or is it?
How are things at home?
What are you thinking?
We need to dig up more
on this Sam Labon
and his hit man-to-be.
We can't just give
the DA what we have now?
Yes. not this DA.
No. we've got to have
exchange of money.
and otherwise the hit's
not credible on their eyes.
We just have to wait for him
to make a move.
Will you make a move?
This is my move.
Huzzah.
Ooh.
Hey. Okay. so we have peas.
salmon fillets and cookie dough.
Yes?
Right.
Does a rock star
live here or something?
Hmm?
I saw the guitars
in the bedroom.
Rock star? No.
You might be one day.
-I wish.
-Oh. come on.
You got the hair already.
and I can see it now.
Anx-ridden rocker
with her athlete
superstar brother.
Now. go share this cookie dough
with your brother. okay?
If he's good.
Hey.
You think we'll be safe here?
Yes. I think
we'll be safe here.
Okay.
I'm going to go
for a little walk.
What?
What? You just said
we'll be safe here.
Yes.
Okay. I'll come with you.
No.
I need to clear my head.
-Dee.
-It's fine.
I'll be fine.
-No. I'm sorry.
I'll give you space.
I'll give you a lot of space.
It'll take a step back.
but I'm coming with you.
-Okay.
Yeah.
-You guys are good?
-Yes. we're chilling.
I'll be back in a bit. okay?
All right.
- Take it from me.
Oh. you think you've got skills?
Oh. You've got skills. huh?
Come on. come on.
Take it. take it. take it.
- Oh. look at that.
- Come on. you've got skills.
You've got skills. huh?
Good job.
There you go.
Hey. what are you making.
Natasha?
-Natasha.
-What are you making?
She's making a moat.
She's protecting the castle.
The princess is in the castle.
we've got to protect her
from the monster
and the sand monster.
Oh.
Wave to the camera.
Hi.
You think the sand monster's
going to get mom?
The sand monster's going
to get Mom.
Uh-huh.
you're not getting Mama.
The sand monster's going
to get you.
Mama's not going anywhere.
360. I love this woman.
Hey. who wants to go swimming?
-Me.
-Let's go swimming guys.
-Hold on. hold on.
Before you do that. come on.
Come here. come here.
No Brandon. come here.
Yes.
You're going to get
all sunburned
and then you'll cry
to mommy later.
so.
Why don't you put
some clothes on?
Cover yourself. okay?
What?
Your ass is hanging out.
people are staring at you.
Come on.
You okay?
It's a bathing suit.
We're at the beach.
You like men staring at you?
Huh?
-Be careful. guys.
-Put some clothes on.
now.
Now.
Come on. guys.
Race to the ocean.
Let's go.
On your mark. get set. go!
Come on.
I got you something.
Guess which hand?
I'm not in the mood
to play games right now. Sam.
Just let me. let me. let me--
What is that?
It's for you.
Just a little something.
that's all.
I'm sorry about the beach.
I just don't like other men
staring at your body.
I want you all to myself.
Sorry.
It's beautiful.
You're beautiful.
Thank you.
Thanks for apologizing.
It means a lot.
Ah. wash your hands first.
This is all from today?
What?
The grocery bill.
It's a lot for one day. no?
Oh. yes.
Kids like to eat
like their daddy.
You don't have to go
to the expensive grocery store.
You get organic this.
organic that.
I'm just buying
the healthier options.
Go to the regular
grocery store.
like everybody else.
I work really hard for my money.
so it'd be nice
if you didn't throw it around
like it was nothing. right?
Okay. Sam.
I'll buy cheap groceries.
How about that?
-Okay. don't say it like that.
Don't say it like that.
like I'm cheap.
I just bought you a nice gift.
I pay for this house.
I pay for the kids' clothes.
I pay for everything
around here. so.
As if I don't pay bills.
it's not just you. you know?
Okay. what do you pay for?
You still owe me $10.000
from the business loan.
Your shitty business
that's getting nothing.
I can smell alcohol
on your breath.
I'm not doing this right now.
We'll talk
about it another time.
Don't walk away from me.
We talk about it when I want
to talk about it. okay?
Stop.
You're hurting me.
Stop it.
You should go cook
your expensive dinner. okay?
Come on.
Cook your expensive dinner.
Cook it.
You think I'm cheap?
See what you make me do?
Huh?
-Mama?
-Mommy?
She's fine.
Hey. Mom's okay.
She fell.
Okay?
Tell them you're fine.
Go to your room. she's fine.
Go to your room. now.
Well. you do have
severe disc bulges
at multiple levels.
L4. L5. and L5. S1.
Oh. with spinal
cord encroachment.
so that could mean surgery.
All things considered.
I think you're very lucky.
These kinds of injuries
can lead to paralysis.
How did this happen exactly?
She was cooking in the kitchen.
dripped over one
of the kid's toys.
and went right
into the countertop.
These bruises on your arms.
they're not from today.
She's a clumsy one. this one.
Two left feet.
but I still love her.
It looks like you'll be doing
the cooking for a while.
until she heals up.
I'll have to barbecue.
Kids like barbecue anyway.
-There you go.
We do have some insurance
forms to fill out.
Could you take Mr. Labon
to the admin window. please?
Just to make copies
of your driver's license.
That's okay.
I like to stay with my wife.
I can do it on the way out.
Well you know.
she's still going to be here
when you get back.
You good?
Yes.
I love you.
Mrs. Labon. it's not my place.
but these injuries tell
a different story.
I just want to make sure
you're okay.
I can get you help
if you need it.
I...
Look who I found.
They were attacking
the vending machines
with grandma.
They were worried about you.
- Mom. are you okay?
Yes.
Go ahead. give her a snack.
She's probably hungry.
She didn't eat dinner.
Hi there.
Yes. Mommy's okay.
You're right. Doctor.
It's not your place.
Sí. está bien.
What do you mean? Look around.
Look at what
you've accomplished.
I'm so proud of you.
Sometimes I forget
how far we've
actually come from.
It's been such a long journey.
I wish I could do more.
Oh. and this little guy.
Yeah. of course I did!
This is for you.
The full loan you gave me.
plus interest.
Hey.
You know. I'm just... I'm trying
to figure out how I got here.
What led me to this. you know?
I mean...were there signs and
red flags?
Yes.
From the very beginning.
Gosh. I looked past this
so many times.
His drinking. his temper.
the manipulations.
Even right now. I don't want
to believe that he's--
A monster?
Hey.
It's not your fault.
I wish I met you sooner. Max.
Before him.
Would have been nice
to be with someone normal.
It's not too late.
I can't lose
if you're the cheater.
Hey.
-Hey.
Look what we found. a cheater.
-Twister.
-Where'd you get that?
Found in the garage.
I am in the most uncomfortable
position right now.
-Oh.
-Yes. I want to play.
All right. well.
then you are left-hand green.
Left-hand green.
I can't even find green
because Brandon's covering it.
All right. I'm left foot red.
Here we go.
-Left hand.
Oh. I can't. Wait.
and you've got to get away.
Spinning again.
Everyone okay?
What is that?
Wait. don't touch it.
don't touch it.
What is that?
It's a pacifier.
I don't get it.
What?
You stay back. stay back.
What the hell?
Max.
Natasha had
a green pacifier just like this
when she was a baby.
Do you think
he's trying to send a message?
Do you think he knows
where we are?
I don't know.
It can't be.
Oh my God.
I do know
that we should pack up
and we should get
out of here right now.
-What?
-Yes.
-We can't just keep running.
-We just got here.
We have to keep moving
until we know it's safe. okay?
Nowhere is safe. Mom.
Can't the police
just do something?
Look. just pack your bags
and let's go. okay?
I'll call the detective.
Come on.
just stay away from the window.
Let's pack. come on. let's go.
This is the best room we have.
I'm sure you'll find
the place comfortable.
Oh. yes. it's perfect.
Honestly.
thank you both so much.
Oh. don't be ridiculous.
I don't have to remind you
that you saved my life.
The least I can do is return
the favor.
and for your kids.
we have some wonderful parrots
that might cross around here
for you to feed.
Oh. wow. look at that.
Cool.
Enjoy your stay.
Thank you.
I hope no one snores.
Yes.
We delivered the package.
Good.
You know my associate had to go
to five different stores to find
the green one.
Make sure you don't lose them.
Who's this associate of yours?
He's a private detective.
He's got a knack
for finding people
that don't want
to be found.
Trust me. you're in good hands.
Just looks like she's
on a little road trip
with her boyfriend out there.
Boyfriend?
Yes. some guy named Max.
dark hair.
You know him?
We need to move this up.
When can we do it?
When you pay me.
This ain't Applebee's.
you don't pay me after you eat.
Okay.
How do you want it. crypto?
Venmo is fine.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Cash. no trails.
and we meet in person.
Fine.
Tomorrow it will be
in Woodland Park.
I'll have it. you be there.
Yes. who's ready to go
to go to the park?
- Yay. can I go to the slide?
Of course you can. buddy.
come here.
Of course you can.
Let's go ahead. bud.
Keep it coming.
What are you drawing?
I'm drawing a horse
holding a watermelon.
-Oh. that's really nice.
-Sam.
Mama is making
watermelon for you.
Sam.
Why don't you let me take them
to the park?
Let me spoil them.
That's why I'm here
for after all.
No. it's okay.
I want to take them.
Sam. you better let me.
You take a rest.
We'll have dinner together
when we are back.
Why?
You know why.
No. I don't.
Are you driving there?
No. I'm thinking horse.
Come on. guys. let's go.
Come on. let's run to the park.
is a rotten egg. let's go.
Sam.
I beg of you. please.
let me drive them.
You're embarrassing me. okay?
Move.
-No.
I'm not a child. okay?
Then stop acting like one.
Sam.
Sam. it's me.
Sam!
It's me.
Grandma.
Come on.
let's go.
It's okay. come on. let's go.
Come on.
come. it's okay.
Come on. Brandon. let's go.
Are you kidding me?
I'm so sorry.
It's fine.
I'm fine.
No.
I'm so sorry.
I'm fine.
but this. Darya.
this has to stop.
For the love of God.
for the sake of the children.
they need a stable environment.
And...
It just reminds me of home.
I know violence.
especially violence
against women.
When it starts.
it never stops.
I'm afraid for you.
I'm so sorry for you.
I am so sorry for you. my love.
Are you out
of your fucking mind?
My mother.
My fucking mother.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
How dare you fucking touch
my mother?
How fucking dare you?
In front of my children.
You crazy asshole.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
This was my last straw.
I can't fucking take
this anymore.
I am fucking done.
You either move
the fuck out of the house
or I'm taking the kids
and I'm leaving.
I am done.
You hear me? I'm fucking done.
You fucking piece of shit.
I'm fucking done.
-You're. you're right.
you're right.
-Don't touch me.
Please.
I can't control it.
You have to help me.
-It doesn't matter.
-I need your help.
I need you. please help me.
Please. you can help me.
-No. I can't. I'm done.
-I don't want to be like him.
He used to hit me.
Please don't do this.
- Help me.
No. please!
Please.
Please. please.
I need help.
I don't want to be a monster.
help me.
The first thing I want to ask
each of you is why are you here?
My husband needs help.
He drinks
and he gets
very violent and abusive
when he's drunk.
and sometimes he doesn't
even remember the next day.
That's why he's here.
Why are you here?
I guess I'm here
so you can help him.
fix him somehow.
I can't go on like this anymore.
Why don't you fix her?
I don't have a drinking problem.
She is the problem.
her and her mother.
and they create these problems.
and then it makes me want
to drink sometimes.
You said you wanted to change.
Is this how you planning
to do it-
-Okay. but don't do that.
don't throw everything on me.
--by getting angry
and blaming me for this?
-It takes two people. you know.
Darya?
-Then why you get--
Why don't we take a breath?
You claiming
everything isy fault
all of a sudden right away?
-Why don't we take a breath.
okay?
Because the first thing
we're going to work on
is communication and listening
and we do that from coming
from a place of compassion
and love.
We do a little exercise
with you guys.
First. I want you to just
a little closer to each other.
Just face each other. all right?
Look into each other's eyes.
Wonderful.
Don't lose eye contact.
and then one at a time.
and that you are ready to listen
and hear what they have to say.
I'm sorry. this is stupid.
Come on. Darya.
This is $200 an hour?
I could stare at you home
for free.
It's just you promised
you would give it a chance.
I know. but this is dumb.
Look at her.
She's not going to help.
Yes. but you said you're going
to take this seriously.
-She is not helping.
-How is this not helping?
Like staring at her is going
to help everything-
Give it a chance. Sam.
-is going to poof. everything
is going to be better?
You know what.
this is dumb. Darya.
I'm not doing this. I'm done.
You know what?
You two do your yoga shit
and get in touch
with your feelings. okay?
I'm finished. I'm done.
-Please?
-No. I'm done.
Can I just ask you one question
before you go.
All I ask is
that you answer honestly yes
or no.
Have you had anything
to drink today?
Fuck you.
Sam.
Listen to me.
You want to leave me?
You can.
but I get the kids.
you understand?
I will do everything in my power
to make sure of that.
I get the kids.
You're late.
Yes. well.
good thing I didn't get paid
by the hour.
You got my money?
Thats subtle.
How do I know you're not going
to run off with it?
You don't.
You want me to leave
my scooter for collateral?
Just get it done.
Sam Lebon. freeze.
Police.
Don't move.
Don't even think about it.
Lie on the ground.
Get on the ground right now.
On the ground.
Arms out like a cross.
Do not move.
do you understand me?
Acknowledge.
Do you understand me?
Yes.
All right. move in.
Sam Lebon. you're under arrest
for conspiracy to commit murder.
All right. get him out of here.
All right. Detective.
I did what you asked.
so that makes us square. right?
Yes. well. congratulations.
First arrest as an informant.
Keep your nose clean
and it won't come back
to bite you
on the ass in county.
I ain't going back.
Let's hope not.
Hey. you live in LA.
you can always be an actor.
Commercials pay well.
Commercials pay well?
That was good.
Hello.
We got him.
What?
Yes. we just arrested Sam
for conspiracy to commit murder.
It's over.
Oh my God.
They got him.
What?
How?
How? How did this--
Let's just say your informant
was
was more than cooperative
when he realized
we could have him
on unrelated charges.
Okay. I have no idea
what you had to pull for that.
but thank you.
Thank you so much.
Hopefully the DA will file
and you'll have your day
in court.
Just be sure you bring
your own attorney
just in case.
Yes. of course.
Thank you. Manny.
Thank you.
You're welcome. Darya.
Do we get to go home?
He was really going to do it.
He was actually going
to go through with it.
He was actually--
I know.
We're okay now.
It's okay.
I love you guys.
- We're helping build
safer communities by addressing
the root cause
of criminal behavior instead
of donning out punishments.
These measures hold
people accountable
but also honor
the rights of human beings.
Is the public safe then?
Concerning that. like I said.
safer communities.
safer streets. safer society.
- At a press conference today.
District Attorney Gonzalez
defended his controversial
sentencing policies.
which critics call pro-criminal.
Okay.
- For the People
versus Lebon.
due to the DA's new
prosecution guidelines
for attempted assault.
the bail has been set
for $25.000.
I'm aware that even though
the police filed solicitation
for murder.
the DA's office
decriminalized it
and filed solicitation
for assault.
Is that correct?
Yes. Your Honor. unfortunately.
but the People
request the defendant
to be held in custody
with no bail.
Your Honor. pursuant to 1271.
my client is in fact
entitled to bail
because he poses
no threat to the community.
The defendant
was recorded hiring
a contract killer.
He emphasized that he wanted
our client damaged
or permanently disabled.
Your Honor.
it would be completely unfair.
quite frankly unethical.
to send a man
with a medical condition
to prison.
Your Honor. this is a farce.
We have a victim impact letter
on behalf of the victim
from her mother.
Your Honor. I object.
This is new information.
Objection is overruled.
I'll allow it.
Mrs. Davoodi. please.
Okay.
Greetings and gratitude
to the honorable judge
of the court.
This is not a complaint.
nor is it an objection.
We are still in a state
of shock and disbelief
about what is going to happen
to our daughter.
Darya.
She was supposed to be attacked
and all the bones
of her delicate body
were supposed to be crushed.
Why?
What did she do wrong?
Who would be able to commit
such a horrible crime of killing
someone slowly
and in the most heinous way?
What if he would have been
successful with his plan?
Where would our daughter be now?
What would her death do
to the soul of her children?
Who would care for the children?
This crime would have crushed
and destroyed
three generations of us.
our children.
and our grandchildren.
Why?
What did she do to deserve this?
How can we live in peace
and have faith that this crime
will not happen again?
How could we.
as elderly parents.
live in peace without fear?
How can we live
when our children
are in danger
at every given moment?
All we request from you.
Your Honor.
who is the representative
of justice.
is to protect our children
and our family.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I'll make my ruling
after I review the recordings.
You may be dismissed.
How is this even possible?
He was in jail for six days
and they let him out
with an ankle monitor?
How much was his bail?
At first it was only $25.000.
Can you believe that?
Then after when the judge heard
all the recordings.
then he raised it to $1 million.
but it doesn't even matter now.
He posted it. he's out.
How is this even legal?
He threatened to have you beaten
and killed and even have it
on tape.
Are your kids
with your parents?
Yes. they're with my mom.
Do you want me to stay?
No.
Thank you.
I just need to be alone
for a little while.
I know.
The nightmares will go away.
I can promise you that.
It will just take some time
It feels like
they're just beginning.
I know.
My attorney said that
the current DA's policy
is either three years
with three years probation
with treatment
for his alcoholism
and psychotic episodes.
or two to three months in prison
with no treatment.
If he goes to jail
for a few months.
he's only going
to come out worse.
If I can't sleep now.
what am I going to do then?
I'm so sorry. Darya.
Thanks for being there.
You must be so sick of me
by now.
Never.
We're going to get
through this. okay?
I hope there's
no hard feelings.
You son of a bitch.
You set me up.
What do you want?
Apology?
I kill people for a living.
Cops cut me a deal.
They say to give them something
or serve time
on a previous charge.
Good for you.
What do you want?
We got unfinished business
to attend to.
Still want your wife dead?
You already got that money.
All right. shoot them.
My life's over anyway.
It don't have to be.
They got me on tape.
I'm all over the news.
I'm stuck in this house
with this ankle bracelet.
and you're here.
so tell me how it gets better.
We stick to the plan.
You get the money
again.
Except this time it's double.
I do the deed and disappear.
You got your ankle bracelet
as an alibi.
No.
Now get the fuck out
of my house.
Think about it.
Why would I come back here
to set you up again?
Already did that.
I'm trying to do something
mutually beneficial
that gets us both out
of this fucking mess.
Cops were watching me before.
Now they think I flipped.
so they won't
even see it coming.
I kill her. get rid of the body.
and disappear.
No body. no crime.
All they got on you is a tape.
With nobody to pressure charges.
You want your life back?
Or
You can see me
on the witness stand.
You watch your pretty
ex-wife try to ride off--
Are you trying
to fucking blackmail me.
huh?
What'd be the fun in that?
I'm offering you the deal
of a lifetime.
Your choice.
Since I'm such a nice guy.
you can even pay me
when it's done.
I want her dead.
You understand?
I want her hurt bad.
Really bad like she hurt me.
When you're done.
call me.
I want to hear her last breaths.
Be in touch.
Hi.
I'm fine.
They're hanging in there.
Are you kidding me?
Is she okay?
Can we get her out?
Okay.
maybe I can reach out
to my charity partner.
Love you too.
You just feel better.
sweetheart.
I will see you soon. okay?
- Gracias. doctora.
Adios.
Hey.
Are you ready?
Hello. hello.
I got us reservations
at Mossimo's.
then I thought
maybe we could go dancing.
you can watch me
embarrass myself.
-Hi.
Oh. wow.
Thank you.
These are beautiful.
Yes.
I just have to-
I just have to change.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
That sounds fun.
Okay. I know you.
You don't have to put
a brave face on.
What's going on?
Things have gotten really bad
in Iran.
My brother told me
that they arrested my cousin.
We were trying to get her out
this whole time
and I just found out
that it's too late.
I'm so sorry.
Me too.
Hey. look. all right.
forget all that.
Why don't we stay home?
We can eat here.
We can relax here.
I'll get us a bottle of wine
and we can just cuddle up
in our own bubble here. okay?
Just you and me.
That sounds nice.
-That sounds nice?
-Yes.
That sounds better.
I'll be back.
Okay.
Max?
Who is it?
- Don't scream.
You'll just make it worse.
Put that knife down.
Who are you?
I'm sure you know.
Put that knife away.
Go ahead. toss it.
Toss that knife over there.
You know. your ex-husband.
not a very nice man.
He's adamant
that I break some bones.
make you scream.
but that's just not my style.
so you do what I say
and I'll make it quick.
How much
did he pay you for this?
Enough.
Please.
just listen to me. okay?
My kids are going
to be home soon.
Please. I don't want them
to get hurt.
I don't want them
to see this. please.
We're just going to go
for a little ride.
Just me and you.
Nice and easy like. okay?
-Okay.
-You don't get stupid
and your kids won't find
your brain splattered
all over these walls.
So let's go.
Hey. babe.
Wasn't able to find
your favorite.
but I did find your second--
Surprise.
- No.
Stop.
Stop it.
No.
Do it.
Do it. goddammit.
The fuck are you waiting on?
9-1-1 what is your emergency?
Now we're done.
No. Sam. you're done.
You're beat.
You piece of shit.
I beat you.
It's over.
You hear me?  It's over.
Police.
He'll wipe that smile off
his face real quick
when he sees where he's going.
Will he?
Hello. hello.
Hey. you.
-Hi.
Okay. can I help with anything?
Can I help with dinner?
Sure.
Okay.
No.
I think
you've done enough.
so it's my time
to take care of you now.
Here you go.
Wow.
I'm certainly not going
to mess with that.
- Yeah.
- Come Here.
Here they are.
Carry on.
How was practice?
Boring.
Boring is good.
I love boring.
Okay.
One big boring family.
You okay with that?
Yes. I'm okay with that.
-Cheers.
It's a one big awesome family.
come one.
There you go.
Manny?
Hey.
Just calling to check on you.
I'm so glad you did.
Let's just hope
the DA files this time.
huh?
Yes.
Listen. thank you so much
for going above
and beyond for me.
Not everyone
would have done that.
A long time ago.
I had this case
come across my desk.
This woman. she was married
to a pretty high-profile surgeon
in LA.
She was scared for her life.
Gave the usual protocol.
She begged me.
She simply pleaded.
Then she said none of the laws
would stop this guy.
I told her to file
a restraining order
and that there was
nothing I could do.
A couple of days later.
I got the call
and I showed up
and I found her husband
sitting on the edge of the bed.
He was covered in blood.
she was lying lifeless
on the floor.
She was long gone.
I should say.
I made myself a little promise
that I'd never break the law
to save someone's life.
but I would certainly maneuver
around it.
Had I done that for her.
that woman would be alive today.
Wow. you really are good
at telling
these bedtime stories.
Yes. it's kind of my thing.
I'm glad you're safe.
Go live your life.
You've earned it. Ms.Davoodi
So have you. Detective.
Take care.
- Now. before we begin.
I need to know.
are you on any medications.
any history of mental illnesses?
- No.
Then we can begin.
- Sit down.
-Okay.
Aho.
Those lessons
make us who we are.
When we learn
to let go of the anger.
hatred. pain.
we realize that every person
is a reflection of what we need
to heal within ourselves.
Why do I have to feel
all their pain?
Why?
To see the pain in others
is to heal the pain within you.
I can't.
I need help.
No. please.
No. please. Daddy.
- No. please. Daddy.
- I need help.
- Stop. please.
Let go.
I can't.
Send them love.
♪ Heartbeat of our mothers. ♪
♪ See the power to forgive. ♪
♪ Fathers sky up so high. ♪
♪ Send them love
and let them fly. ♪
[Melody -When you
find compassion
for the brokenness of others.
you can truly forgive them.
Then they no longer have
any power over you.
It's so hard.
The world has thrown
everything it could at you.
From when you were a child
with a war in Iran.
to your journey to America
for a better life
all on your own.
You have endured so much.
You're no stranger to pain.
You have suffered betrayal
at the hands of the man you wed.
and through all of that.
you still stand
for what is right.
You stand for compassion.
empathy towards others.
So much so you've made it
your life's mission.
Rise above any pain
and imagine yourself
still smiling.
That is true power.
How do you feel?
Free.
The women's freedom movement
in Iran
is an ongoing struggle
for gender equality
and civil rights
for over four decades now.
Women are victims
to discrimination laws related
to divorce.
child custody. and inheritance.
Women
die for their right to protest
in our quest for justice.
but what happened
to my daughter here.
this kind of abuse
is not limited to Iran alone.
Sadly. it is happening
all over the world.
Maybe to the people we see
every day.
They may even be our friends.
My beloved daughter is here
to talk about her journey.
Thank you all so much
for being here.
Unfortunately. there is
no satisfying conclusion
to my story with my ex-husband.
If he had sought help
for his childhood traumas
or his battle with alcoholism.
perhaps we could have saved
our family.
but instead. it led him down
a very dark path.
Despite his attempts
to have me harmed
or even killed.
he was released from prison
after just a few days.
Now for almost three years.
he's been living freely while
my children and I remain
in constant fear.
Through my spiritual journey.
I found a way to embrace
my trauma.
It has been a source of rebirth.
allowing me to forgive.
to heal.
and most importantly.
to reclaim my power.
Today. I am at peace.
and I am happy again.
and I would love
to share that light
to heal and inspire others.
My charity.
Still Smiling.
is dedicated to this mission.
We are committed
to building safe havens
for survivors of abuse
and domestic violence
across the globe.
but that is not enough.
We must do more.
We have to stand for those.
and especially for those
who don't have a voice.
We need to stay united
because together
we can create a better.
a safer world for all of us.
Thank you.